multiplestreamteam.com 2012-03-15

# Global Team Business | Multiple Stream Team

## Privacy Policy 

Multiple Stream Team makes the same firm commitment to privacy for our Web site visitors as for our customers using our web-hosted service. We created this Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Web site, located at (http://MultipleStreamTeam.com the "Web site") and to demonstrate our commitment to the protection of your privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Web site, and not to any other Web sites that you may be able to access from the Web site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. By using the Web site, you are agreeing to the terms of the Privacy Policy. 

## Company Overview

Multiple Stream Team provides a sophisticated software system that allows users to create and manage interactive email and mobile campaigns. Companies use to interact with their target audience using email and using mobile phones through text messages, mobile content such as ringtones, wallpapers, video, and more. 

## Frequency of Program Service 

By opting in to an email or mobile campaign you are agreeing to receive messaging alerts on your mobile phone and emails. Alerts may be sent daily, weekly, monthly, and at scheduled intervals dependant on the email or mobile campaign to which you have subscribed and your mobile carrier's policy. 

##  Notification of Privacy Policy Changes 

We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to revise the Privacy Policy, we will post a notice at least thirty days prior to making any material changes. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. Your continued use of the Web site, including use after the posting of any changes to these terms, will be deemed acceptance by you of the Privacy Policy. 

##  Notice Concerning Children

PLEASE NOTE: We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children's privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Web site visitor is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information regarding that visitor. 

## Information Collection Practices

### What Basic Information Does Collect? 

You can visit the Web site to read information about our company, products, and services without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. In operating the Web site, includes optional information request forms such as White Paper or Webinar Request forms, Newsletter subscription forms, and general contact request forms that request your name, company, title, phone number, email address, URL, address and other information to help us determine your needs related to our products and solutions and in order for you to download or view documents or other information through the Web site. We use this information to send updates about our company and to contact you if requested or necessary. also collects billing information such as credit data via our partner Authorize.net. Depending upon your request, may also ask for additional information, such as how you heard about us. This information is provided by you on a voluntary basis only and is not required by us in order for you to use and enjoy the Web site. We use the information that we collect on the Web site to contact you to further discuss your interest in our company, our services, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as marketing promotions and events. This information may also be used to improve the services we provide you. We use this information to improve the way that we provide our services to our clients, to relay administrative information, and to verify login information. The information is collected and stored in a manner that is appropriate for the nature of the data that we collect, and the need to fulfill your request. does not share, sell, rent, or trade PII with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

## Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. The site stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

## Clients

If you are a client of (or work on behalf of a client), through our secure web interface we also collect your username and password, and any other information that you provide to us on behalf of the client that you are representing pursuant to the terms of a license or other agreement between the applicable client and (the "Service Agreement"). You should refer to that Service Agreement in addition to this Privacy Policy with regard to your use of the Web site and it's privacy obligations. 

## Automatic Collection 

Our servers automatically recognize visitors' IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet), domain names, the activity of the visitor's browser when the visitor is viewing the Web site; the site path of visitors; the time visitors come to the Web site and length of visit. No personal information about you is revealed in the process. The Web site may also gather anonymous traffic data that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer and reserves the right to publish such anonymous, aggregate summary information regarding its visitors for promotional purposes. 

Multiple Stream Team uses "cookies" and "web beacons" to collect data. A cookie is a small text file containing a random and unique identifier that either or its third party web analytics provider on behalf of transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (unless you set your browser to reject cookies) that enables or its third party web analytics provider's system to recognize your browser. Multiple Stream Team use cookies to track your movement through the Web site and verify the login status of client using products or services linked directly within the Web site. Cookies are also used to track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs or to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Neither nor its third party web analytics provider store any personally identifiable information in cookies. Web beacons (also known as clear gifs) are typically a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on a site are used by and its third party web analytics provider in combination with cookies to help us understand how you with the Web site. We use web beacons to measure visitor behavior, to help us improve visitor experience, and to manage site content. 

## Security and Privacy 

Multiple Stream Team web site uses security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We store the information in two redundant databases in two secure environments at different locations with our data hosting service provider, GoDaddy. 

Multiple Stream Team takes care to reinforce the importance of our web site visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Multiple Stream Team requires unique usernames and passwords that must be entered each time a user logs on to it's client interface. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of all data. The bottom line is that, because our business involves hosting application accounts, data security is paramount. We're constantly reevaluating and deploying new technologies to enhance our security. 

In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets. In such transactions, visitor information may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that all or substantially all of it's assets are acquired in a transaction, our visitor information may be an asset that is reviewed and transferred. Such a transaction will be disclosed per the "Notification of Privacy Policy Changes" guidelines above. Also, as with the data we collect on behalf of our clients, we reserve the right to disclose any data we collect at our Web site if required by law or valid order of a court or other governmental authority or to protect the health and safety of 's employees or the general public. 

Multiple Stream Team is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites to which we link. We encourage our visitors to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit. 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## Updating and Choice/Opt-Out 

Visitors who request information on our web site have the following options for reviewing, modifying and deleting any personally identifiable information that has previously been provided to Multiple Stream Team, as well as updating their profiles and unsubscribing (opting out) to avoid receiving future communications from us: 

  * Sending an email message to support at awareus.com. We'll reply within 30 days of receiving your request confirming any corrections or updates requested.
  * If you are subscribed to receive newsletter or commercial emails from us, you may send us a request to unsubscribe from receiving such emails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions within the email. We will comply with your unsubscribe request within 24 hours after receipt of such request (or shorter time period, if required by law). 

## Testimonials

We may post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. 

## Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Please be aware that we, Multiple Stream Team, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

## Legal disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

## Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or this web site, please contact us directly: Email: GlobalTeamBusiness@gamil
